[🎄 12 Days Of Christmas Deals

Shop Now](https://4patriots.com/category/gift-guide)

Search

Search

    ###### Featured Deals

    [](https://4patriots.com/product/ultracharge-patriot-power-generator-2000x-sidekick-bundle)["Ultracharge" Backup Power Package](https://4patriots.com/product/ultracharge-patriot-power-generator-2000x-sidekick-bundle)﻿
    
    [](https://4patriots.com/product/ultracharge-patriot-power-generator-2000x-sidekick-bundle)["Ultracharge" Backup Power Package](https://4patriots.com/product/ultracharge-patriot-power-generator-2000x-sidekick-bundle)﻿
    
    ###### Deals

    [
    
    B1G1 Mini Generator Deal](https://4patriots.com/product/supercharge-patriot-power-generator-1800-sidekick-bundle)[
    
    FREE 72-Hour Food Kit](https://4patriots.com/product/72-hour-emergency-survival-food-kit)[
    
    "Mini" Cooler & Warmer](https://4patriots.com/product/freedom-fridge-electric-cooler-warmer)[
    
    #1 Emergency Kit for Cars](https://4patriots.com/product/patriot-power-all-in-one-emergency-car-kit-95-pieces)

    ###### Check Out Our Gift Guide For More Savings

    ###### Featured New Arrivals

    ###### Summer-Sweet Fruit Lasts 25 Years

    ###### Featured Best Sellers

    ###### Our Most-Powerful Solar Generator Ever

    ###### Categories

    [
    
    Solar Generators](https://4patriots.com/page/emergency-solar-power/portable-solar-generators-power-stations)
    
    [
    
    Solar Panels](https://4patriots.com/category/solar-power/solar-panels)
    
    [
    
    Upgrade & Expansion Packs](https://4patriots.com/category/solar-power/generator-upgrade-kits)
    
    [
    
    Best Sellers](https://4patriots.com/category/solar-power/solar-power-best-sellers)

    ###### Backup Power When The World Goes Dark

    ###### Categories

    [
    
    Emergency Food Kits](https://4patriots.com/page/emergency-survival-food-kits)[
    
    Time-Based Food Kits](https://4patriots.com/category/emergency-food-kits/time-based-food-kits)[
    
    Specialty Food Kits](https://4patriots.com/category/emergency-food-kits/speciality-food-kits)[
    
    Best Sellers](https://4patriots.com/category/emergency-food-kits/emergency-food-best-sellers)

    ###### Includes 2 FREE 72-Hour Food Kits

    ###### Categories

    [
    
    ](https://4patriots.com/product/patriot-pure-ultimate-water-filtration-system-nanomesh-filter)
    
    [###### Now Certified to Reduce More Dangerous Contaminants than Ever
    
    ](https://4patriots.com/product/patriot-pure-ultimate-water-filtration-system-nanomesh-filter)

    ###### Categories

    ###### "Super Survival" Solar Air Conditioner

    ###### Categories

    ###### Best Seller

    ###### The Gift of Preparedness

    ###### Featured Deals

    [](https://4patriots.com/product/ultracharge-patriot-power-generator-2000x-sidekick-bundle)["Ultracharge" Backup Power Package](https://4patriots.com/product/ultracharge-patriot-power-generator-2000x-sidekick-bundle)﻿
    
    [](https://4patriots.com/product/ultracharge-patriot-power-generator-2000x-sidekick-bundle)["Ultracharge" Backup Power Package](https://4patriots.com/product/ultracharge-patriot-power-generator-2000x-sidekick-bundle)﻿
    
    ###### 🎁 Gift Peace of Mind

    [
    
    "Mini" Cooler & Warmer](https://4patriots.com/product/freedom-fridge-electric-cooler-warmer)[
    
    B1G1 FREE Mini Generator](https://4patriots.com/product/supercharge-patriot-power-generator-1800-sidekick-bundle)[
    
    Boil Water With Only the Sun](https://4patriots.com/product/sun-kettle-solar-water-heater)[
    
    TSA-Approved Power Bank](https://4patriots.com/product/patriot-power-cell-cx-portable-solar-power-bank)

    ###### Our Gift Guide Has All Your Loved Ones Covered

[](https://4patriots.com/page/policies/privacy-policy)[Home](https://4patriots.com/) / Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

### Last Updated: May 1, 2024

4Patriots LLC (“4Patriots,” “4P,” “us,”, “we” or “our”) respects your privacy. We developed this Privacy Policy to explain how 4P collects, uses, shares, and protects Personal Information (defined below), and your choices about the collection and use of Personal Information.

This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information collected or processed through www.4patriots.com and any other 4P-operated website or social media page that links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Site”).

### What is Personal Information?

﻿“Personal Information” is information that identifies or relates to a particular individual. Examples of Personal Information include, among others, name, email address, phone number, mailing address, and online identifiers.

### Types of Personal Information We Collect and Use

We may collect and store Personal Information that you provide to us online (e.g., while on the Site or in responding via email to a feature provided on the Site). We collect Personal Information from our users via the Site during online registration and online purchasing. Generally, this information includes name, phone number, and e-mail address for registration or opt-in purposes and name, shipping address, email address, and credit card information when purchasing our products or services.

We collect the following types of information automatically through your use of the Site: Cookies, Device Identifiers, and Similar technologies. When you use or access the Site, 4P and our service providers use cookies, device identifiers, and similar technologies such as pixels, web beacons, and local storage to collect information about how you use the Site. We process the information collected through such technologies, which may include or be combined with Personal Information, to help operate certain features of the Site, to enhance your experience through personalization, and to help us better understand the features of the Site that you and other users are most interested in.

Most browsers provide you with the ability to block, delete, or disable cookies, and your mobile device may allow you to disable transmission of unique identifiers and location data. If you choose to reject cookies or block device identifiers, some features of the Site may not be available or some functionality may be limited or unavailable. Some of our service providers may use cookies or other methods to gather information regarding your use of the Site, and may combine the information in these cookies with any Personal Information about you that they may have. The use of such tracking information by a third party depends on the privacy policy of that third party. 

To assist us with analyzing our website traffic through cookies and similar technologies, 4P uses third-party analytics services.

The Site uses cookies to help keep track of items you put into your shopping cart including when you have abandoned your cart and this information is used to determine when to send cart reminder messages via email and SMS (if you have previously opted in to receiving SMS messages from 4P).

We may engage third parties, including social media platforms, who use cookies, pixel tags, and other storage technologies to collect or receive information from the Site and elsewhere on the internet to provide marketing services to us, including targeted advertising.

When you use our Site, our servers automatically record information, including your Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”), browser type, referring URLs (e.g., the site you visited before coming to our Site), domain names associated with your internet service provider, information on your interaction with the Site, and other such information (collectively, “Log File Information”). We may also collect similar information from emails sent to you which then help us track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients.

We use Log File Information collected from our implementation of the Site to help secure the Site by identifying potential threats and vulnerabilities and in analyzing the effectiveness of our Site to improve the Site’s function and content.

### How We Use Personal Information

﻿In addition to other uses notified to you, 4P may use Personal Information for the following purposes:

* Administering and operating your account;
* Providing customer service or support;
* Processing payments and fulfilling orders;
* Analyzing, administering, and improving the Site;
* Enabling secure use of the Site;
* Sending information and promotional materials;
* Protecting our rights or our property;
* Meeting legal obligations; and
* For other purposes related to the reasons for which you provide Personal Information.

### Disclosure of Personal Information

We will not disclose Personal Information except as set forth in this Privacy Policy or with your consent. This section describes to whom 4P discloses Personal Information and for what purposes:

Trusted Service Providers: We engage third parties to perform tasks on our behalf and to assist us in operating the Site and providing our products and services. This may include but is not limited to affiliates, service providers, consultants, advisors, marketing and advertising partners, and joint marketing partners. For example, 4P may engage third parties to process payments (such as credit card processors and payment plan providers), provide services (such as extended warranties), and perform other activities (such as order fulfillment) on our behalf. This may require 4P to share Personal Information (including financial information) with third parties, who may store and use such Personal Information. We take commercially reasonable steps to help ensure our service providers provide at least the same level of protection for Personal Information as 4P does, however, your Personal Information collected by such third parties is subject to the third party’s privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, such third party’s collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information.

Corporate Transactional Partners: If 4P sells or otherwise transfers or merges part or the whole of our business or assets to another organization, any information collected through the Site, including Personal Information, may be among the items sold or transferred.

Legal, Compliance and Regulatory Matters: We may disclose Personal Information at the request of law enforcement or government agencies; in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; to establish, protect, or exercise our rights; to defend against a legal claim; to protect the rights, property, or safety of any other person; or as otherwise required by law.

### How We Protect the Confidentiality of Personal Information

We protect the confidentiality and security of information 4P obtains in the course of business. We use commercially reasonable safeguards, such as industry-standard encryption technology, to help keep the information collected through the Site secure.

Despite these efforts to store Personal Information in a secure operating environment, 4P cannot guarantee the security of Personal Information during its transmission or its storage on our systems. Further, while 4P attempts to ensure the integrity and security of Personal Information, 4P cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third parties such as hackers from illegally obtaining access to Personal Information. We do not represent or warrant that Personal Information about you will be protected against, loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties.

### Accessing, Updating, or Deleting Personal Information

If you would like to access, update, or delete Personal Information about you, you may submit a request here. We will promptly review all such requests in accordance with applicable law.

### Opting Out of Receiving Electronic Communications

We may send notifications, promotions, or other information via email or text message (“Communications”). You may choose to stop receiving Communications by following the instructions provided in a Communication (for example, by clicking “Unsubscribe” in an email or replying STOP to an SMS text message). If a Communication is necessary for us to provide you a requested product or service, 4P may not be able to provide you with an opt-out. 

The 4P mobile message service (the "Service") is operated by 4P. Your use of the Service constitutes your agreement to these terms and conditions (“Mobile Terms”). We may modify or cancel the Service or any of its features without notice. To the extent permitted by applicable law, 4P may also modify these Mobile Terms at any time and your continued use of the Service following the effective date of any such changes shall constitute your acceptance of such changes. By consenting to 4P’s SMS/text messaging service, you agree to receive recurring SMS/text messages from and on behalf of 4P through your wireless provider to the mobile number you provided, even if your mobile number is registered on any state or federal Do Not Call list. Text messages may be sent using an automatic telephone dialing system or other technology. Service-related messages may include updates, alerts, and information (e.g., order updates, account alerts, etc.). Promotional messages may include promotions, specials, and other marketing offers (e.g., cart reminders). You understand that you do not have to sign up for this program in order to make any purchases, and your consent is not a condition of any purchase with 4Patriots LLC. Your participation in this program is completely voluntary. We do not charge for the Service, but you are responsible for all charges and fees associated with text messaging imposed by your wireless provider. Message frequency varies. Message and data rates may apply. Check your mobile plan and contact your wireless provider for details. You may opt-out of the Service at any time. Reply by text using the single keyword command STOP or click the unsubscribe link (where available) in any text message to cancel. You'll receive a one-time opt-out confirmation text message. No further messages will be sent to your mobile device, unless initiated by you. If you have subscribed to other 4P mobile message programs and wish to cancel, except where applicable law requires otherwise, you will need to opt out separately from those programs by following the instructions provided in their respective mobile terms. For Service support or assistance, text HELP to the number provided within the text or contact us using the information provided in the “Contact Us” section of our Site. We may change any short code or telephone number 4P uses to operate the Service at any time. You acknowledge that any messages, including any STOP or HELP requests, you send to a short code or telephone number 4P has changed may not be received and 4P will not be responsible for honoring requests made in such messages. The wireless carriers supported by the Service are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages. You agree to provide 4P with a valid mobile number. If you get a new mobile number, you will need to sign up for the program with your new number. To the extent permitted by applicable law, you agree that 4P will not be liable for failed, delayed, or misdirected delivery of any information sent through the Service, any errors in such information, and/or any action you may or may not take in reliance on the information or Service. 

### Retention of Personal Information

We will retain your Personal Information for at least as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which your Personal Information has been collected as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We also may retain Personal Information to the extent required by law.

### Personal Information Transferred from Outside the U.S.

If you are using the Site from outside the United States, please be aware that Personal Information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States. Although 4P takes steps to provide adequate safeguards, the data protection laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using the Site, you consent to your information being transferred to the United States for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. 4P does not specifically target its products or services at individuals in the EU and is not subject to GDPR.

### State-Specific Privacy Rights

﻿Some States have enacted consumer privacy laws that grant their residents certain rights and require additional disclosures. This State-Specific Privacy Rights section addresses these requirements and serves as our California notice at collection. As a resident of one of these States (currently, California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah, and Virginia), you have specific rights regarding the personal information 4P collects, uses, and shares.

1. Categories of Personal Information Collected: 4P collects a variety of personal information, including identifiers, geolocation data, internet activity, consumer profiles, electronic data, commercial information, professional information, and similar related data.
2. Usage and Disclosure: This personal information is utilized for various business purposes and shared with service providers as necessary. Additionally, usage information may be collected and potentially “sold” (as defined under your State’s privacy law, for example, the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) for California residents), for which you have opt-out rights.
3. Your Rights:

* Right to Know: You can request details about the categories of personal information 4P has collected, the sources of that information, specific pieces of personal information we hold about you, and how we use and share that information.
* Right to Delete: You have the right to request the deletion of your personal information that 4P has collected.
* Right to Opt-Out: You can opt out of the sale of your personal information and the use of your personal information for interest-based advertising.

4\. Exercising Your Rights: To exercise any of the above rights, please complete [this form](https://4patriots.com/page/frequently-asked-questions). 4P may reasonably require additional information to verify your identity before we can process your request.

5\. Non-Discrimination: 4P will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your privacy rights under State law.

Certain States may provide similar rights to residents to access, rectify, delete, or port their personal information, and the right to appeal decisions regarding such requests. These requests can be made through [this form](https://4patriots.com/page/frequently-asked-questions).

If you have any questions or need further assistance regarding your rights or our privacy practices, please contact us using the information provided in the "Contact Us" section of our Site.

### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect or solicit any Personal Information from children. In the event that 4P learns that 4P has collected Personal Information from a child, 4P will promptly take steps to delete that information.

### Other Websites, Including Social Media

We are not responsible for the practices employed by any websites or services linked to or from, or utilized through, our Site, including the information or content contained within them. A link to a third party’s website should not be construed as an endorsement. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing Personal Information to third parties.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it periodically. Unless otherwise indicated, any changes to this Privacy Policy will apply immediately upon posting to the Site.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Site, please contact us using the information provided in the [“Contact Us”](https://4patriots.com/page/support) section of the Site.

100% Satisfaction Guarantee

USA-Based Customer Service

Easy Payment Plans 

We Support Our Troops & Veterans

##### We Champion Freedom & Self-Reliance

Customer Care

More Ways to Shop

About Us

Join our list for early access to deals & new products!

Testimonials featured on this site are from real people. Sometimes names & pictures are changed to protect their privacy & safety; some were given free products in exchange for honest feedback. Testimonials represent exceptional results, don't apply to the average purchaser, and don't guarantee that you'll achieve results. Cade Courtley is a former Navy SEAL who served 9 years of active duty and has been compensated by 4Patriots for his hard work in helping us test and endorse products. The United States Military (including the U.S. Navy SEAL Team) and other organizations, publications and people referenced on this site, are not affiliated with 4Patriots. They have not endorsed, sponsored or recommended this product; no affiliation or endorsement is claimed.

2024 © 4Patriots LLC - All Rights Reserved.
